<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UPCOMINGTRADER</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/</link><description>Recent content on UPCOMINGTRADER</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:57:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.upcomingtrader.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:41:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/contact/</guid><description>We would love to hear from you! Whether you have a question, comment, or concern, feel free to reach out to us using the information or form below.
contact at domain dot com
Follow Us You can also follow us on social media platforms.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:41:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/about/</guid><description>If you learn to lose gracefully, you too can learn how to trade like a professional. Check out our social platforms.
Let&amp;rsquo;s learn to trade better, together!</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:11:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy
Last updated: 2023
1. Introduction
Welcome to Upcomingtrader (&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data. This Privacy Policy will inform you how we handle your personal data, your privacy rights, and how the law protects you. Please use the Glossary to understand the meaning of some of the terms used in this Privacy Policy.
2. Data We Collect About You</description></item><item><title>Who Was Jesse Livermore: Unraveling the Enigmatic Mind of Wall Street's Most Legendary Trader and His Enduring Legacy</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/who-was-jesse-livermore-unraveling-the-enigmatic-mind-of-wall-streets-most-legendary-trader-and-his-enduring-legacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:57:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/who-was-jesse-livermore-unraveling-the-enigmatic-mind-of-wall-streets-most-legendary-trader-and-his-enduring-legacy/</guid><description>Jesse Lauriston Livermore (1877-1940) was a legendary American stock trader and investor who gained fame and fortune through his remarkable market speculations during the early 20th century. Known for his keen intuition and understanding of market psychology, Livermore was one of the most influential and successful traders of his time.
From Rags to Riches: The Remarkable Early Life of Jesse Livermore, Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s Trading Prodigy Jesse Livermore, a name synonymous with stock market success and trading mastery, did not have an easy start in life.</description></item><item><title>Before Pivot Points Jesse Livermore Pivotal Point</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/before-pivot-points-jesse-livermore-pivotal-point/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:57:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/before-pivot-points-jesse-livermore-pivotal-point/</guid><description>Before the concept of pivot points was introduced in technical analysis, Jesse Livermore had already developed his own method for identifying key price levels or pivotal points in the market. Livermore&amp;rsquo;s pivotal points were based on his observation of price action, and he used these points to determine potential entry and exit points for his trades.
Livermore&amp;rsquo;s approach to pivotal points relied on his understanding of market psychology and the behavior of other traders.</description></item><item><title>How to Use Jesse Livermore Trading Method for Sustained Futures Trading</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/how-to-use-jesse-livermore-trading-method-for-sustained-futures-trading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:42:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/how-to-use-jesse-livermore-trading-method-for-sustained-futures-trading/</guid><description>Jesse Livermore, one of the most famous traders in history, developed a trading method based on his years of experience and observation of market behavior. His method was built on several key principles and rules that he believed were crucial for successful trading. While Livermore traded stocks, his insights can still be applied to various markets; such as futures trading and all timeframes. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some key aspects of Jesse Livermore&amp;rsquo;s trading method.</description></item><item><title>Inspirational Jesse Livermore Trading Quotes</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/inspirational-jesse-livermore-trading-quotes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:28:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/inspirational-jesse-livermore-trading-quotes/</guid><description>Jesse Livermore A True Trading Pioneer Livermore&amp;rsquo;s life story has been well-documented in the book &amp;ldquo;Reminiscences of a Stock Operator&amp;rdquo; by Edwin Lefèvre, which is a fictionalized account of Livermore&amp;rsquo;s experiences. Although the book&amp;rsquo;s protagonist is named Lawrence Livingston, it is widely understood that the character is based on Livermore. Throughout his career, Livermore developed trading principles and strategies that remain influential today. His wisdom on market trends, risk management, and the psychology of trading is still studied and admired by traders and investors alike.</description></item><item><title>What Are Jesse Livermore Principles in Trading</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/what-are-jesse-livermore-principles-in-trading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 18:48:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/what-are-jesse-livermore-principles-in-trading/</guid><description>Who Was Jesse Lauriston Livermore Jesse Lauriston Livermore was an early stock trader and investor who had an aggressive trading style. Many of the insights that Jesse pioneered still hold some value today when trading the markets.
He started trading right out of grammar school at the young age of fourteen. Maybe his many years of experience around trading lead to his aggressive trading style. He was a board boy at a Boston stock brokerage.</description></item><item><title>Introduction To Futures Trading For Beginners and Advanced Traders</title><link>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/introduction-to-futures-trading-for-beginners-and-advanced-traders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 01:16:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.upcomingtrader.com/blog/introduction-to-futures-trading-for-beginners-and-advanced-traders/</guid><description>Trading Futures Investment Risk Warning If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting started with futures day trading, there are quite a few things that you should consider before getting started. Below I will give an introduction to futures trading by doing a thorough overview of some main topics and dive deeper into each topic where I will explain trading futures, define trading futures, how much to start trading futures to make sure that you have a solid foundation for your futures trading career.</description></item></channel></rss>